discountholidays.com 2009-06-28

# Holidays - From cheap all inclusive package holidays to luxury holiday deals

## » Our Commitment to Privacy

Holiday.co.uk and its owner Holiday Express Ltd are committed to protecting the privacy of those using the Holiday.co.uk web site and the confidentiality of the personal information which our customers provide us with. We use the information we collect to provide services and to ensure that your booking is processed smoothly. Beyond that we only use personal information if volunteered by you. Holiday.co.uk will never sell personal information or share personal information with third parties unless these are involved to fulfil your holiday or flight booking.

At Holiday.co.uk we use the information we collect in the following ways:

• When you place a booking through Holiday.co.uk, we need to know your name, e-mail address, delivery address, name(s) and number of passengers, credit or debit card number and expiry date. This allows us to book your holiday or flight and to keep you up to date on the dispatch of tickets and payment progress.

• So that we can make the experience with Holiday.co.uk as good as possible and provide you with over and above service, Holiday.co.uk store with your consent personal information and information about the booking and the use of our services. 

• With your consent we may also use your contact information to let you know about enhancements to the site, special offers and competitions. 

• If you respond to a promotion or competition we will ask for your name, address and e-mail address. This is so that we can fulfil the promotion, notify competition winners and track the popularity of our marketing activity. 

## » Holiday.co.uk Will Never Sell Personal Information

Holiday.co.uk will never sell personal information or share personal information with third parties, unless these are involved with the fulfilment of your booking or without your consent. Our employees and associated companies are obliged by us to respect confidentiality.

## » Your Personal Information Is Safe With Holiday.co.uk

At Holiday.co.uk, data security is one of our highest priorities and we do our utmost to protect the data you provide. When you book online or access your booking details, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us.

## » Phone Call Monitoring

During telephone enquiry and booking, we occasionally record the phone call for training purposes only. Your conversation will not be passed on to any other company or used for any other means except training. 

## » Changes to Policy

All changes to the privacy policy in the future will be highlighted in this section. This privacy policy v1.0 was last updated on 8th May 2001.

## » Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Holiday.co.uk uses cookies to recognise when you return to Holiday.co.uk. Cookies also enable us to gain information about the use of our services and to enhance our site according to the preferences of our customers. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information.

## » Further Questions

Should you have further questions regarding our privacy policy, please refer by e-mail to **[feedback@holiday.co.uk](mailto:feedback@holiday.co.uk)**.

Our customer service also helps you if you need information about your data or if you would like to have data corrected. If a change of our privacy policy should become necessary you will always find the actual version on this page.

Holiday.co.uk welcomes your questions and comments about privacy, please send e-mail to **[feedback@holiday.co.uk](mailto:feedback@holiday.co.uk)**.

## » Our postal address is:

**Holiday.co.uk**

**118 Travel Ltd.**  
23 New Mount Street  
Suite 2-3  
Manchester  
M4 4DE
